Pitbull - Rain Over Me (feat. Marc Anthony)
Album:Planet Pit (2011)
SUB BY KRISHNA P S
Girl my body don't lie,
Red One,
I'm outta my mind,
Let it rain over me,
Mr. Worldwide
I'm rising so high,
out of my mind
So let it
rain over me
Let it
Always a new million,
always a new vodka
Forty is the new 30,
baby, you're a rockstar
Dale veterana,
que tu sabe,
Mas de la cuenta,
no te hagas
Teach me
or better yet,
Freak me baby,
yes, yes
I'm freaky,
baby
I'mma make sure that
your peach feels peachy baby
No bullshit rods,
I like my women
sexy classy sassy
Powerful yes,
They love to get the middle,
nasty
This ain't a game
you'll see,
You can put
the blame on me
Dale muñequita
ahora ahi,
And let it
rain over me
Girl,
my body don't lie,
I'm outta my mind,
Let it
rain over me
I'm rising so high,
out of my mind
So let it
rain over me
Let it
Always a new million,
always a new vodka
Light is the new majority,
ya tu sabe
Next step
la casa blanca
No hay carro,
no vamo en balsa
Mami you know
the drill,
They will know what I got
'til they read the will
I ain't tryin',
I ain't trying to keep it real
I'm trying to keep wealthy
that's for real
Pero mira
que tu estas buena,
Y mira que tu
estas dura
Baby no me hables mas,
y tiramelo mami chula
No games
you'll see,
You can put
the blame on me
Dale muñequita
ahora ahi,
And let it
rain over me
Girl,
my body don't lie,
I'm outta my mind,
Let it
rain over me
I'm rising so high,
out of my mind
So let it
rain over me
Let it
Mr worldwide,
Marc Anthony,
tu sabe
I was playing
with her,
She was playing
with me
Next thing you know,
we were playing with three
I was playing
with her,
She was playing
with me
Next thing you know,
we were playing with three
Rain over me
Girl,
my body don't lie,
I'm outta my mind,
Let it
rain over me
I'm rising so high,
out of my mind
So let it
rain over me
Let it
sub created by krishna p s